weltpixel.com 2019-02-25

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how WeltPixel uses and protects any information that you give WeltPixel when you use this website. WeltPixel is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. WeltPixel may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

## Key Terms of Privacy Policy:

  * **Who is covered by this Policy?**

Online visitors to WeltPixel.com as well as customers, excluding end users of the WeltPixel billing/subscription platform and related tools.

Please note that use of this website / application is not allowed for individuals who are under the age of 16 years.

  * **What Information do we collect?**

Depending on who you are and how we are serving you, we may collect information including full name, email, phone number, organization address, billing address, card address, IP address, and other information collected by customer through custom fields, if any.

  * **How do we use this information?**

To provide customer service, to complete your transactions, to provide you billing services, and to periodically contact you for transactional as well as marketing purposes. We may also use your information for our business accounting and tax purposes.

  * **Who else may access this information?**

In addition to authorized WeltPixel personnel who may access your information for the purposes discussed in this policy, some of our third party vendors may also have access to your information. Vendors of the sub-processors may also have access to your information.

  * **Do we use Cookies?**

Yes, we do. We also may collect log files for behavioral advertising (which you can opt out of). This includes information relating to website usage, analytics services (such as Google), and IP information for performance monitoring.

  * **How can you exercise your rights as a data subject?**

Most rights can be exercised by contacting us at  _[support@WeltPixel.com](mailto:support@WeltPixel.com)_. Other rights such as rectification of your data can be exercised through your account’s self-service portal. Data portability requests may be directed to our support staff at [support@WeltPixel.com](mailto:support@WeltPixel.com).

  * **How will we keep you informed of changes to this Policy?**

We periodically review this Policy and will endeavor to notify you of any changes by email. However, please continue to check this page for updates.

## What information do we collect?

We collect personal and non-personal information from you when you register on our site, setup your domain and/or configure your details. When ordering or registering on our website application, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, business name and/or credit card information.

## This refers to:

  * **Account Information:**

Including First Name, Last Name, Email, Phone Number, Organization Address, Billing Address, and Internet Protocol (IP) addresses

  * **Billing Information:**

First Name, Last Name, Email, Phone Number, Billing Address, Shipping Address, and Locale.

  * **Credit Card Information:**

First Name, Last Name, full PAN and Card Address.

  * **Custom Fields:**

Any other personal information, if stored by customer in the course of business.

## On what basis do we collect your information?

In most cases, we collect your information on the basis of your desire to avail a particular service from us or to complete a transaction using our platform. Therefore, our processing in many cases occurs on the basis of your consent or the need to perform a contract that we may have with you (also on behalf of your end users). However, in addition to collection on the basis of consent, there are other bases on which we may collect or process your information. These are as follows:

  * We collect and also store your personal data as part of our legal obligation for business accounting and tax purposes such as in relation to record-keeping, compliance, disputes, and filings.
  * We will occasionally send you product updates where we have assessed that it is beneficial to you as a customer and in our interests. Such information will be non- intrusive and is processed on the grounds of legitimate interests.
  * On the basis of your opt-in, we will send you updates related to events, webinars, blogs and other marketing and promotional activities where we have assessed that it is beneficial to you as a customer and in our interests.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To improve customer service**

In the context of customer support your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests.

  * **To process transactions**

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * **To send periodic emails**

The email address you provide in the application, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your usage, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Transport Layer Security (TLS) technology and then stored into our database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at [support@WeltPixel.com](mailto:privacy@WeltPixel.com).

Personal data we collect is stored on infrastructure provided by Nexcess.Net, LLC

## Do we use cookies and other tracking technologies?

What are Cookies? Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

What do we use Cookies for? WeltPixel and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. Analytics services we use for these purposes are those provided by Google.

Log files. As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site. We may also use your IP address for application performance monitoring and for blocking anomalous usage.

Behavioral Targeting. We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

## Do we share any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  * **Service Providers**

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service or processing your payment. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. In addition, your merchant may have also enlisted third party service providers to help serve you.

  * **List of sub-processors authorized to process customer data for WeltPixel**

WeltPixel uses a range of third party sub-processors to assist them in connection with the Services (as described in the Privacy Policy). These third party sub-processors include:

  * **Entity Name**

Nexcess.Net, LLC

Zendesk, Inc.

Intuit, Inc.

Mailchimp, Inc.

  * **Legal Obligations**

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

## User Access and Choice

Upon request WeltPixel will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, request deletion of your personal information, or withdraw provided consent by contacting us at  _support@WeltPixel.com_.

Some rights such as rectification/correction of your data can be exercised through your account’s self-service portal.

Please note that, in relation to billing services to customers, the personal information we collect is that which is provided to us by customers we work with. In such cases, please contact the concerned customer (your service provider) for more details. If you are not sure about your service provider, you can get in touch with us at  _support@WeltPixel.com_.

You may also contact us to confirm if we are processing any information relating to you. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

## Data Retention

We will retain your information as needed to provide you services. If you close your account with WeltPixel, we will still retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, financial/audit requirements, to resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. However, we will identify your account in our database as “deleted” or “closed”.

## Opt-out Preferences

When you register for an account, we will use your name and email address which you have opted-in to send periodic emails to you of both promotional and transactional in nature. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at support@WetlPixel.com

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online  _privacy policy._

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
